Guide to Northern Arizona University Catalogs, etc. Cubb.00084
Cubberley Education Library
Northern Arizona University (formerly Northern Arizona Normal School, formerly Northern Arizona State Teachers College, formerly Arizona State College Flagstaff)
1901-1977
Cubberley Education Library
Cubb.00084
71 item(s)
Located in Flagstaff, Arizona. Founded in 1899 as Northern Arizona Normal School. Changed to Northern Arizona State Teachers College in 1925. Became Arizona State Teachers College in 1928 and Arizona State College of Flagstaff in 1945. In 1966 renamed Northern Arizona University.
Teachers colleges; Arizona
- Northern Arizona Normal School, 1901-1925; 16 item(s) Catalogs for 1901/02-1903/04, 1908/09, 1911/12-1913/14, 1915/16-1916/17, 1920/21-1921/22, 1924/25
  - Northern Arizona Normal School Summer Session, 1908-1921; 4 item(s) Bulletins for 1908, 1916, 1920, 1921
- Northern Arizona State Teachers College, 1925-1929; 9 item(s) Catalogs for 1925/26-1928/29
  - Northern Arizona State Teachers College Summer Session, 1927-1929; 4 item(s) Bulletins for 1927, 1928, 1929 Poster 1929
  - Progress and Problems, 1928; 1 item(s) Reports by college president & dean
- Arizona State Teachers College, 1929-1945; 33 item(s) Catalogs for 1929/30-1944/45
  - Arizona State Teachers College Summer Session, 1930-1943; 17 item(s) Catalogs for 1930-1931, 1933-1940, 1942-1943 Posters for 1930, 1932. 1935, 1936 Graduate Courses 1937
  - Arizona State Teachers College Bulletin Pictorial Number, 1936; 1 item(s)
- Arizona State College Flagstaff, 1948-1965; 9 item(s) Catalogs for 1948/49, 1952/53, 1954/55, 1959/60, 1963/65
  - Arizona State College Flagstaff Summer Session, 1948-1952; 2 item(s) Catalogs for 1948, 1952
  - Arizona State College Flagstaff Graduate Study, 1963-1965; 2 item(s) Catalogs for 1963/64, 1965
- Northern Arizona University, 1966-1977; 4 item(s) Catalogs for 1966/67-1967/69. 1975/77 Graduate Bulletin for 1975